The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
Asta and the others traveled to the Heart Kingdom
to learn more about the Devil's curse.
But Asta was abducted,
leaving Noelle, Mimosa and Finral
to do battle with the spirit guardian, Gaja.
Meanwhile, Asta was forced into a confrontation as well
against a powerful water spirit by the name of Undine.
You may address me as Undine.
I'm one of the four great spirits
and I'm contracted to the Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
Andine and Gaja both presented serious challenges
for Asta and his companions.
But...
Sealing magic, inverse relief!
Here's the deal!
We can't just back down after watching you show up!
Mind if I join you?!
I have a real soul.'"
Coolzentical music
I love you!
I want you to play together today!
Yeah yeah
強く風吹く世界の果てで
僕らは今日も目を閉じる夢を見る飽きもせず
今は小さく儚い希望も
いつか時代を変えてゆく光になると信じて
背負うべきものなど何一つないさ
全て抱きしめてゆく
例えばそれが痛みだとしても
叶うなら君と共に
この声がこの喉が擦り切れるほど今叫ぶよ
未来は自分で切り開くんだって
とめとなく溢れ出る情熱のままさ
歩き出そう
To save my dream
ご視聴ありがとうございました
That's weird
I could have sworn I sensed somebody's key here
Hey
Oh my gosh I am so sorry
This thick beaver pelt just felt so nice and soft on my skin
What was that for?
Oh where did my glasses go?
Laura Pechka?
What in the world are you up to now?
I told you to hurry up and change out of your pajamas
We have guests
Right
I apologize
So that girl's the queen of the heart kingdom?
I only survive thanks to my defensive spell
It appears she was holding back
What a great talent
As for the others
He's so fast
Please forgive my rudeness
I forced you into a battle with me
So that I could accurately judge your magic stages
Uh
Magic stages?
Is that the scale I heard about before?
Where the smaller the number is
The more capable you are?
Yes
Here strength is judged by magic power
Not the number of bows
For example
If there was one mage ranked very high on the scale
He might be victorious against dozens of lesser opponents
At the same time
So in a war between magical nations
Each side is generally judged by the magic stages of their military forces
More specifically
A kingdom's power is typically determined by the number of mages it has who are ranked near stage zero
Of course
If it's a devil you're dealing with
Any fighter who's lower than stage one won't be able to hold their own
A devil?
That's why we're here
The thing is
We came because we picked up a huge curse signal
And a devil's gotta be the cause of it
How did they find out something only spirit guardians should know?
Can you guys tell us anything about devil curses?
Always so direct
Unfortunately for you
No one will ever talk about them
Actually
I happen to suffer from a devil curse myself
If nothing's done about it
I'll be dead within a year or so
Honestly!
Why?
Why would you tell them that, fool?
Huh?
Oh sweet Laura Petchka
That adorable ignorance of yours will be the end of me one day
I just know it
It's true
The reason we brought the two of you to this place against your will
And tried to discern your magic stages
Is because we desire to defeat Megicula
The devil who cast this curse
Clearly you stand to benefit from this as well
So, residents of the Clover Kingdom
Please join us
Yeah?
What's wrong?
Excuse me
I forgot to water the poplata trees
Really?
I'm pretty sure we were in the middle of a life and death conversation here
But hey, do what you gotta do, I guess
If this is the way their queen behaves
Then I'm very concerned about them
Whoa, this is so crazy
Okay, here you go
Drink up
Oh my
The Zozo squirrels are as energetic as ever
Uh-oh
Slow down there, Michele
It's dangerous if you run too quickly
It looks like old man Kakalos' cop is starting to clear up now
And look, the total fruits are growing so splendidly as well
It's good to see everything going smoothly
She's watering the whole place at once
She sees the entire kingdom at a glance
And single-handedly controls the water
She has an all-encompassing warmth about her
So no living thing in her domain goes uncared for
This magic is fitting for the queen of the Heart Kingdom
Now, now, Laura Petschka
How about we change you into more appropriate attire?
You see, our current ruler has inherited the ability of most of the queens who've gone before her
She's our beautiful kingdom's guardian deity
The all-knowing priestess
Therefore, we simply cannot lose someone as precious as her to a devil's curse
There is no one else like her
That's better
You're quite pretty when you put in the effort, you know
Oh, it's hard to walk in this
Come on!
What am I going to do with you?
Hey, I get it
The clumsiness must be part of the devil's curse too, huh?
Oh no, I'm just naturally a klutz
Wow, that's bad!
Megicula
That loathsome devil who cursed my dear Laura Petschka
Is currently in the Diamond Kingdom
We came to scout the Diamond Kingdom to be safe
What happened?
He wiped out all of those Diamond soldiers on his own
And some of them were as tough as our captains
Who is this guy?
Don't you go getting any bright ideas, Luck
As much as I hate to admit it
I've never felt like this in my whole life
Believe it or not
I don't want to fight this guy
I'm so relieved that you're safe
You're the worst
Stop getting kidnapped
It's starting to get really old
Her Majesty the Queen is here
She's so majestic
And the magic that she possesses is immeasurable
So that's the Queen of the Heart Kingdom
Wow, talk about a treat for the eyes
How lucky am I to be in the presence of such an exceptional goddess
Wait, stop it, Finral
You're supposed to be better than that
You're a one-woman man from now on
Remember, get it together, would you?
What's going on?
Is Finral okay?
Nope
Residents of the Clover Kingdom
I humbly ask that you lend your strength to us
Really?
Come now, Laura Petchka
Do try to behave more like a queen
Oh, a nosebleed
Aw, you're still adorable
What happened?
I got blood on my dress
Of course
All right, give me a moment
This is precisely why I was so against her conducting this meeting in person
I guess now that that's over
What did you need our help with?
I was under the impression that the Heart Kingdom had plenty of mages at Stage 1 or higher
Not to mention the Spirit Guardians
So what can we do?
As I explained, when battling a devil
Every mage involved needs to be ranked at least Stage 1 in order to keep up
But even a Zero
Still wouldn't have what it takes to achieve victory
You see, Spirit Guardians are able to wield powerful magic by borrowing energy from natural mana
But they cannot defeat a devil
Unlike us, your kingdom created magic types that are not derived from nature
Such as chain, steel, and the eccentric spatial magic
In exchange, they lose the divine protection of natural mana
And some of the Irregulars who were born in that environment
Have the necessary traits to best a devil
One example of this is Julius Nova Crono who possesses time magic
There is also the Black Bull's Captain Yamisuke Hiro and his dark magic
Unfortunately, it appears the majority of Julius' power has been used up at this point
She knows about that?
I wonder how much information she has
And you
Asta and Nero
For combat, Nero's about a Stage 6
But she's got ancient sealing magic and is used for Bidden Magic
Asta has no mana
But because of that, he was granted the use of Anti-Magic
People like you two who possess unique, inexplicable powers are referred to as Arcane Stages
So... we're...
I would like you to lend us your Arcane powers to help us defeat that devil
And as a reward, I will happily share any information that I have with you
But we don't have the authority to make a major decision like that
Good thing we've got this magic item then, huh?
I'm taking a dump here
Oh, you have something important to ask me?
Well, I happen to be doing something important myself
In fact, this could be one for the history books
Call back later
He just hung up on me
Pooping is crucial
You're on his side?
You mustn't say such vulgar things, Laura Petchka
Well, I had my suspicions that something like this would happen
So I borrowed a magic item that allows us to connect with the transmission magic that Marx uses
Good thinking
Nice one, Mimosa
Alright, let's try it out
Mimosa, did something happen?
Wait, is that who I think it is?
Oh, wow, you must be the Queen of Heart Kingdom
So what kind of magic do you use?
Please don't pop into a frame like that, Your Majesty
Have you forgotten about your condition?
People will see
Well, you just called me Your Majesty
So now they know it's me
Huh?
That's no big deal
The Queen already knew
What?
So, anyway
She says they need our help to beat a devil
Because we're arcane stager or something like that
That's fine by me
You and your friends could gain something amazing from all this
Honestly, I think I'd like to be over there helping you myself
That's out of the question
I suppose that settles it then
How wonderful
Then again, if you tried to fight a devil in your current state
You would all be slaughtered in the blink of an eye
That's kind of blunt
I mean, is the spade devil really supposed to be that impossible to take down?
Yes
Even more deadly than the devil you fought with previously
Worse than him?
We only won that time because we had help from super powerful people
Like the first wizard king and the leader of the elves
And even then it was a close call
Megicula is responsible for the scar on Gaja's face
What?
But we barely stood a chance against that guy before
Ah yes, I remember dueling with that spirit guardian fellow in the past
He's extremely skilled
You guys fought?
So even someone the wizard king speaks that highly of isn't able to defeat this devil?
The way we are now, we can't win
We have to get stronger
Megicula is currently haunting the spade kingdom
And using its citizens to gather up enormous amounts of power
Soon, that devil could invade and conquer not only the heart kingdom
But clover and diamond as well
If nothing changes
Then I will eventually be killed by this curse
That's why I'd like to invade the spade kingdom before my power becomes too weak
We can take half a year
Let's make our forces as strong as we can
We should enlist any mages who stand a chance in battle against a devil
Train for six months
Then we will fight together to stop Megicula
If you help us
We can do it!
Sir, are you certain you approve of this?
Remember
The magic knights are still exhausted from fighting the elves
It's true that we have half a year
But this is a devil
Just think of the casualties
For clover and for heart
I take it you heard the report from the scouts we sent out, Marks?
Considering the state diamond is in
Our only hope is to have our magic knights improve their skills
I'm sure the queen of the heart kingdom knows that as well
I guess you're right
Assemble all of the magic knight squad captains
Sir!
How long is Captain Yami gonna make us wait?
We've got a major announcement to make here
Keep your voice down, you little shrimp
We all know that the captain can't do his business if he doesn't have peace and quiet
Pooping again?
Whew, Nelly
Wait a minute, don't tell me you've been in there since we called you
The war's not over yet
Trust me, I'd love to kick back and celebrate today's victory
But the next battle's already starting to rear its ugly head
Metaphors or not, it's still gross
Well, anyway, let's hear what went down during your visit to the heart kingdom
Oh, yes sir
It was so eventful, I'm not sure where to begin
Get this!
We found out who was cursed by a devil over there and it's the queen of all people!
Pretty crazy, right?
And if the curse isn't broken soon, then she's only got a year to live
Since she was chosen by one of the four great spirits, she's the most powerful mage they've got
If they lose someone like that, they're in big trouble
Obviously we should keep all that on the down low
I hope you at least got a little bit of useful information on the devil, too
We have a name, Megicula
And a location, in the Spade Kingdom
In Spade?
If that's really true, then what we saw makes a lot of sense
Huh? Did you guys find something weird?
Apparently when they went to check out the Diamond Kingdom, they ran into one of Spade's mages close to the border
Whoa, really?
Except, he wasn't just a normal mage
There were hundreds of Diamond soldiers on the ground
He beat them all by himself like it was nothing
And that cold, dark magic he had
I wouldn't be surprised if he got it from a devil
I don't know if it's possible, but I wonder if we might have seen Megicula without even realizing it
Oh no, if that's him, then the Diamond Kingdom is...
Pretty much done for, all because of that one guy
But Mars...
Even from that distance, one thing was obvious
That man could have easily killed us
If we had picked to fight with him, we'd have suffered the same fate as those Diamond soldiers
Yeah, you're not tough enough yet
If we can't defeat that devil, then both the Heart Kingdom and the Clover Kingdom are going to be history
So the only solution is to try to get stronger
The Queen told us to spend six months training
And after that, the Heart Kingdom will launch their attack on the Spade Kingdom
As Magic Knights, it's our job to spend every minute of the next six months getting as powerful as we can
And then we'll be able to help them defeat Megicula and keep everybody safe
One thing
What is it, Sora?
Just so we're clear, are you sure training is all we have to do?
Because beating a devil is hard even for the best of us
Unless we're Stage 1 mages or higher, we won't even be able to keep up
To put that into terms that we're more familiar with
That would be like a first-class Senior Magic Knight
No, even that wouldn't be good enough in this situation
Wait a minute, are you telling us we have to get up to a Vice-Captain's level in just six months?
Heh, easier said than done
Unfortunately, as far as we know, the only people in our Kingdom who stand a chance of defeating the Devil
Are mages whose power lands them in the Arcane Stage
Including Asta, Nero, Captain Yami, and the Wizard King
Well, whether I have what it takes or not, I refuse to give up
We can all get there eventually
Right?
I have to
Megicula is the one who killed my mother
Hear that?
Put your big boy pants on
The Royal just said that she's not gonna give up
And since we outrank her, we're not allowed to chicken out, you got it?
Yeah
That wasn't like me, huh?
After all, our friend's life is on the line, so I can't afford to give in to fear
Wait, what friend is this now?
I'll do everything in my power to make myself a Stage 1 mage
That way I can look out for my bestest buddy, Asta
I forgot!
If I don't do something about this Megicula thing soon, then I'm gonna be sentenced to death!
How could you forget?
I guess there's no choice then
No self-respecting Magic Knight would let a devil run wild and do whatever it wants, right?
Well, alright! I'm in!
I have no idea what I can do to help out
But I'll try my hardest!
I'll use these six months to make myself an even more powerful mage and get rid of that terrible curse
Maybe then I'll be worthy of Lady Phenis' heart
After we stop Megicula and the curse has been broken, I want to talk to Nozel again
About our mother
All that matters right now is beating that devil
And then maybe I can understand a little more about my own devil, too
For the sake of their futures and this world, I can't let another devil take control
Okay, for the next six months, I'm just gonna let the Black Bulls loose
Which means you can do what you want
So you get to go wherever, team up with whoever
Your only mission is to build up your strength
Remember, this is a devil in the Spade Kingdom we're dealing with
Train like your life depends on it
Because I'm gonna kill you if you don't
Now, I usually tell you to do this in the heat of a battle
So six months should be plenty of time
Push past your limits, Black Bulls!
Right!
There's no reason I'm proud of your life
You look smart at some times
Every night what happens
There's no reason I'm serious
You don't care
I don't see
You look smart at some time
Cause you know
You don't have to beء
tutte
What happens
Maybe
何度
Thank you.
間違いを間違いで終わらせないで
涙を涙で拭わないで
確信があるその心をかさげんで
ここならもう一人じゃない
This isn't just about us
It's a life or death situation
for the Heart and Diamond Kingdoms too
Black Clover page 130
The new Magic Knight Captain Conference
Let's prepare ourselves
to face that devil in the Spade Kingdom